[
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: hallo",
        "Antwort": "hello"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: tschues",
        "Antwort": "bye"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: essen",
        "Antwort": "eat"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: laufen",
        "Antwort": "walk"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: rennen",
        "Antwort": "run"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: reden",
        "Antwort": "talk"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: sprechen",
        "Antwort": "talk"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: du",
        "Antwort": "you"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: ihr",
        "Antwort": "you"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: ich",
        "Antwort": "me"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: land",
        "Antwort": "country"
    },
    {
        "Level": "mittel",
        "Frage": "übersetze: ich esse",
        "Antwort": "i eat"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: trinken",
        "Antwort": "drink"
    },
    {
        "Level": "mittel",
        "Frage": "übersetze: ich liebe",
        "Antwort": "i love"
    },
    {
        "Level": "mittel",
        "Frage": "übersetze: ich habe",
        "Antwort": "i have"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: mama",
        "Antwort": "mum"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: mutter",
        "Antwort": "mother"
    },
    {
        "Level": "mittel",
        "Frage": "übersetze: o mein gott",
        "Antwort": "o my god"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: neu",
        "Antwort": "new"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: schön",
        "Antwort": "nice"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: name",
        "Antwort": "name"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: app",
        "Antwort": "app"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: baby",
        "Antwort": "baby"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: wissen",
        "Antwort": "knowledge"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: lieben",
        "Antwort": "love"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: haben",
        "Antwort": "have"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: machen",
        "Antwort": "make"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: stuhl",
        "Antwort": "chair"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: messer",
        "Antwort": "knife"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: ersetzen",
        "Antwort": "replace"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: arbeit",
        "Antwort": "work"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: himmel",
        "Antwort": "sky"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: dach",
        "Antwort": "roof"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: handy",
        "Antwort": "phone"
    },
    {
        "Level": "leicht",
        "Frage": "übersetze: hund",
        "Antwort": "dog"
    }
]
